Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/lisasu-3ba3364 (LinkedIn)

Lisa Su

Chair & CEO at AMD

Austin, Texas, United States

Summary

I am the Chair and CEO at Advanced Micro Devices, a Fortune 500 technology leader. Since joining AMD, we have successfully executed a transformation of our strategy, market focus, and product execution.

My passion is in leading global technology teams to bring great products and solutions to market.

Prior to joining AMD, I spent 15+ years in the semiconductor industry in various engineering and general management roles at Freescale and IBM.

I currently serve on the Board of Directors of Cisco Systems Inc., the U.S. Semiconductor Industry Association (SIA), and the Global Semiconductor Alliance (GSA).

Experience

AMD

12 years 4 months

Chair & CEO

February 2022 - Present (2 years 3 months)

United States

President & CEO

October 2014 - February 2022 (7 years 5 months)

Austin

SVP & GM, Global Business Units

January 2012 - October 2014 (2 years 10 months)

SVP & GM for AMD's global business units including Client, Server,

Embedded, Graphics, and Gaming businesses.

Freescale Semiconductor

4 years 7 months

SVP & GM, Networking and Multimedia Group September 2008 - December 2011 (3 years 4 months)

General Manager for the networking and multimedia business - home of PowerQuicc, QorlQ, Starcore, VortiQa and the i.MX (ARM) family of processors.

Senior Vice President & CTO June 2007 - August 2009 (2 years 3 months)

Lead global technology R&D for Freescale Semiconductor (Motorola spinoff).

IBM

VP, Semiconductor R&D February 1995 - May 2007 (12 years 4 months)

Led R&D operations for IBM in semiconductor process development including significant new technology innovation. Led global alliances with AMD, Sony, Toshiba, Chartered, Samsung, Infineon.

Texas Instruments

Member of Technical Staff

June 1994 - February 1995 (9 months)

Education

Massachusetts Institute of Technology PhD, Electrical Engineering · (1990 - 1994)

Massachusetts Institute of Technology BS/MS, Electrical Engineering (1986 - 1991)